A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Westmoreland Davis, 1911-1922 (bulk 1918-1922)
Library of Virginia
- Series 1: General Correspondence, 1918-1922., Extent: 61 boxes (27.45 cu. ft.). (Box 1-61)
  - War Correspondence, Local Boards, 1918 August-1920 June. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Local Boards, Letters of thanks, 1919. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, Marine League of the U.S., 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, Medal of Honor, 1919. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, Medical Advisory Board, 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, Memorial for Virginia Soldiers, 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Military, Miscellaneous, 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Military, Negroes, 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, National Guard, 1918-1919. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, National Guard, 1920. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, National Guard, 1921 January-April. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, National Guard, 1921 May-August. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, National Guard, 1921 September-1922 January. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, National Liberty Sing, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, National Slovak Society, 1918-1919. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, Naval Reserve and Navy, 1918-1921. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Officers, Training Camps, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Officers, Volunteers, 1919-1920. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, Pay of Soldiers, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, Pershing, John J., 1920. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Physical Reserve Committee, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, Physicians, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, Police, Military 1918. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - War Correspondence, Provost Marshall General, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - War Correspondence, Public Information Committee, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - War Correspondence, Quartermaster, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - War Correspondence, Recruiting, 1919. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - War Correspondence, Red Cross, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - War Correspondence, Registration, Military, 1918. (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - War Correspondence, Returning soldiers, 1918 November-1919 January. (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - War Correspondence, Returning soldiers, 1919 February-May. (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - War Correspondence, Returning soldiers, 1919 June-1921 May. (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - War Correspondence, Rifles and Rifle Camps, 1918-1920. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - War Correspondence, Seaplane, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - War Correspondence, Selective Service Organization, Discontinuation certificates, 1919. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - War Correspondence, Slackers, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - War Correspondence, Soldier's property, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - War Correspondence, Spies, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - War Correspondence, State troops, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - War Correspondence, Surgeon General, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - War Correspondence, Training Camps, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - War Correspondence, U.S. Military Academy, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - War Correspondence, U.S. School Garden Army, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - War Correspondence, Universal training, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - War Correspondence, Venereal diseases, 1918-1920. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - War Correspondence, Virginia Rifle Range, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - War Correspondence, Virginia Volunteers, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - War Correspondence, War Department, 1919-1921. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - War Correspondence, War Economy Conference, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - War Correspondence, War Review Bill, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - War Correspondence, War Risk Insurance Bureau, 1919. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - War Correspondence, War Saving Stamps, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - War Correspondence, War tax, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - War Correspondence, West Virginia Troops, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - War Correspondence,Win the War for Permanent Peace Convention, 1918. (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - War Correspondence, Women's Organizations, 1918-1919. (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Washington, George, National Victory Memorial Building (Washington, D.C.), 1919-1922. (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Washington, George, Statue by Jean-Antoine Houdon, 1914-1920. (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Washington, George, Statue by Jean-Antoine Houdon, 1921 January-May. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Washington, George, Statue by Jean-Antoine Houdon, 1921 June-November. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Washington, George, Statue by Jean-Antoine Houdon, Photographs, 1921. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Washington and Lee University, 1918. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Water Power League, 1921. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Weights and Measures, Department of, 1919-1921. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - West Point Military Academy, Appointments to, 1918-1921. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia boundary, 1917-1918. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Whooping Cough recipe, 1918. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - William and Mary College (Williamsburg, Va.), 1918. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - William and Mary College (Williamsburg, Va.), 1919-1921. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Witnesses, 1920. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Women, 1918. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Workmen's Compensation Law, 1918 January-March. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Workmen's Compensation Law, 1918 June-1919 April. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners for Accomack County, 1918-1921. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners for Norfolk County, 1918. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners for Northampton County, 1918. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners for Princess Anne County, 1918-1920. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Wrecks, Commissioners, Miscellaneous, 1918. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - YMCA, 1918. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - YMCA, 1919-1921. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Oversize materials. (Box 77)
- Series II: Extraditions and Pardons, 1918-1922., Extent: 16 boxes (7.2 cu. ft). (Box 62-77)
  - Criminal Expenses, Miscellaneous, 1921. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Extraditions A (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Extraditions Ba-Bl (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Extraditions Bo-Bu (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Extraditions Ca-Cl (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Extraditions Co-Cr (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Extraditions D (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Extraditions E (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Extraditions F (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Extraditions Ga-Gl (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Extraditions Go-Gu (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Extraditions Ha-He (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Extraditions Hi (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Extraditions Ho-Hu (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Extraditions I (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Extraditions Ja-Je (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Extraditions Jo (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Extraditions K (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Extraditions L (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Extraditions Mc (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Extraditions Ma-Me (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Extraditions Mi-Mo (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Extraditions N (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Extraditions O (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Extraditions Pa-Pi (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Extraditions Pl-Pu (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Extraditions Q (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Extraditions Ra-Ri (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Extraditions Ro-Ru (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Extraditions Sa-Sk (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Extraditions Sm-Sw (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Extraditions T (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Extraditions U (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Extraditions V (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Extraditions Wa-Wh (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Extraditions Wi-Wy (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Extraditions Y-Z (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Ab-Ad (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Al (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Am-Ay (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Ba-Bl (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Pardons Bo (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Pardons Bra-Bre (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Bro-Bry (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Pardons Bu-By (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Pardons Ca (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Ch-Cl (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Co (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Cr-Cu (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Da (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Pardons De-Dy (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Pardons E (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Fa-Fi (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Fl-Fr (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Ga-Go (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Gr-Gw (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Hag-Han (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Pardons Har-Hat (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Pardons He-Hi (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Ho-Hu (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Pardons I (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Ja-Je (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Johnson (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Jones-Ju (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Pardons K (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Pardons La-Li (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Lo-Ly (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Mc (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Ma-Mi (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Mo-My (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Pardons N (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Pardons O (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Pardons Pa-Pe (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Ph-Pi (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Po-Pu (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pardons @ (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Ra-Ri (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Ro-Ru (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Pardons Sa-Sc (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Pardons Seagle, E.C. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Sh-Sl (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pardons Sm-So (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Pardons Sp-Sy (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Sydnor, Giles (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Ta-Te (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Pardons Th-Ti (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Pardons To-Ty (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Pardons U (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Pardons V (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Pardons Wa-We (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Pardons Wh (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Pardons Wi-Wy (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Pardons Y (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Pardons Z (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Pardons Unknown (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Pardons, Correspondence, General, 1918-1921. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Pardons, Dr. J.T. Mastin files, A-G. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Pardons, Dr. J.T. Mastin files, J-P. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Pardons, Dr. J.T. Mastin files, R-W. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Pardons, Political disabilities, Removal of, 1918-1919. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Pardons, Remission of fines, 1919-1921. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Pardons, Requisitions, 1918-1919. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Pardons, Requisitions, 1920-1922. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Pardons, Requisitions Index Cards (made by other states to Governor of Virginia). (Box 75-76)
  - Pardons, Requisitions Index Cards (made by the Governor of Virginia to other states). (Box 76)
  - Oversize materials. (Box 77)